Guide to the Baltimore and Ohio Employees Relief Association Annual Reports, 1880-1918 MS2077
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Baltimore and Ohio Employees Relief Association annual reports
1880-1918
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Baltimore and Ohio Employees Relief Association
MS2077
0.5 Linear Feet
The Baltimore and Ohio Employees Relief Association was inaugurated on May 1, 1880 and incorporated on May 3, 1882. The organization was established to extend relief to B. & O. Railroad Company Employees and their families in case of sickness, injury, old age and death. Collection contains annual reports from May 1, 1880 until December 31, 1918.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Baltimore and Ohio Employees Relief Association was inaugurated on May 1, 1880 and incorporated on May 3, 1882. The organization was established to extend relief to B. & O. Railroad Company Employees and their families in case of sickness, injury, old age and death. It also advised these recipients in the management and investment of their benefits and offered them personal loans at reasonable interest rates.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains annual reports from May 1, 1880 until December 31, 1918.
Reports and studies; Baltimore (Md.)
- Annual Report, 1880 May 01 -1881 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Report, 1881 January 01 -1882 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1882 October 01 -1883 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1883 October 01 -1884 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1884 October 01 -1885 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Annual Report, 1885 October 01 -1886 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Annual Report, 1886 October 01 -1887 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Annual Report, 1887 October 01 -1888 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Annual Report, 1888 October 01 -1889 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Annual Report, 1889 October 01 -1890 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Annual Report, 1890 October 01 -1891 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Annual Report, 1891 October 01 -1892 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual Report, 1892 July 01 -1893 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Annual Report, 1893 July 01 -1894 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Annual Report, 1894 July 01 -1895 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Annual Report, 1895 July 01 -1896 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Annual Report, 1896 July 01 -1897 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Annual Report, 1897 July 01 -1898 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Annual Report, 1898 July 01 -1899 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Annual Report, 1899 July 01 -1900 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Annual Report, 1900 July 01 -1901 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Annual Report, 1901 July 01 -1902 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Annual Report, 1902 July 01 -1903 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Annual Report, 1903 July 01 -1904 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Annual Report, 1904 July 01 -1905 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Annual Report, 1905 July 01 -1906 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Annual Report, 1906 July 01 -1907 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Annual Report, 1907 July 01 -1908 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Annual Report, 1908 July 01 -1909 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Annual Report, 1909 July 01 -1910 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Annual Report, 1910 July 01 -1911 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Annual Report, 1911 July 01 -1912 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Annual Report, 1912 July 01 -1913 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Annual Report, 1913 July 01 -1914 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Annual Report, 1914 July 01 -1915 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Annual Report, 1915 July 01 -1916 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Annual Report, 1916 July 01 - December 31 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Annual Report, 1917 January 01 - December 31 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Annual Report, 1918 January 01 - December 31 (Box 1, Folder 39)